{
    "id": "45153aa390c5408f8795261e8ebab315",
    "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Hurry up! We ……………………….. for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "are waiting",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa1de3eea56648a2a3da4f049a8757c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What are you ……………………….?' ‘I ………………………. letters.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing, writing",
                "done, writing",
                "doing, write"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a050f854e16b4d1fad2d837c1e0fc02d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. in Italy at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4bb5f8e7ac7d4660a0ee530fcfaa2b77"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t like to be disturbed when she …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "74a749ae8af54037a232bcc9f1136b6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "That child ……………………………… bigger everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "getting",
                "is getting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e2ecffd8ae894cc4b001c16fe5059e6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that girl …………………………….. on the table?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand",
                "standing",
                "is standing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36a7af0c47c44257a82b522c988545ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. for the shops to open.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "am waiting",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2289ab3bb404379932d6ff3a975be92"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. Jane tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f32b124a0e84ec798f08c5003f86090"
        },
        {
            "question": "The universe ………………………, and has been so since its beginning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expands",
                "is expanding",
                "expanding"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6846875a4d143cf8d4de5bd71eba4e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ……………………. at home for the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lives",
                "living",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0e7a1a089a63427caa7a7e8eeab60e71"
        }
    ]
}